Guide to the Records of National Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated, 1949, 1954, 1956, 1958-1993 *I-181 and *I-181A
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Part 2, Series IX: Jewish Communal and ASJM Organizations Correspondence and Information Materials, undated, 1963-1965, 1971, 1973-1992; Boxes 197-280.
  - Subseries A: ASJM-related organization in the U.S., undated, 1963-1965, 1971, 1974-1991; Boxes 197-262.
    - Pittsburg, PA, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1982-1983 (Box 246, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1985-1986 (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, undated, 1989 (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Political Management Resources, 1985 (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Rabbinical Assembly, 1981 (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Rabbinical Assembly, 1983 (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Rabbinical Assembly, 1985-1986 (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Rabbinical Assembly, 1987, 1989 (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Rabbinical Council of America, 1979-1981 (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Rabbinical Council of America, 1982-1986 (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - Rabbinical Council of America, 1987-1988 (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - Radio Liberty, 1984-1987 (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - Ramaz School/Congregation Jeshurun, 1979-1980 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Ramaz School/Congregation Kehillath Jeshurun, 1982 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Rav Tov, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Research Center for Religion and Human Rights in Closed Societies, 1978-1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Rhode Island, 1979-1980 (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - Rhode Island, 1982-1986 (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 248, Folder 7)
    - Rockford Institute, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - San Antonio, Texas, 1984 (Box 248, Folder 9)
    - San Diego, California, 1982-1984 (Box 248, Folder 10)
    - San Diego, California, 1984 (Box 248, Folder 11)
    - San Diego, California, 1985 (Box 248, Folder 12)
    - San Diego, California, 1986 (Box 248, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco, California, 1978-1979 (Box 248, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco, California, 1980-1982 (Box 248, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco, California, 1983-1984 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco, California, 1985 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco, California, January-March 1986 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco, California, April 1986-January 1987 (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - Second Generation, 1981, 1985-1986 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Society for the Study of Religion under Communism, 1981-1982 (Box 249, Folder 7)
    - South Carolina, 1979 (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - South Carolina, 1982 (Box 249, Folder 9)
    - South Carolina, 1984-1985 (Box 249, Folder 10)
    - South Carolina, 1987 (Box 249, Folder 11)
    - South Dakota, 1982 (Box 249, Folder 12)
    - Southern New Jersey, 1979-1980 (Box 249, Folder 13)
    - Soviet Jewry Legal Advocacy Center, 1984 (Box 249, Folder 14)
    - Springfield, MA, 1979 (Box 249, Folder 15)
    - Springfield, MA, 1982-1983 (Box 249, Folder 16)
    - Stamford, CT, 1979-1980 (Box 249, Folder 17)
    - Student Coalition for Soviet Jewry, 1979-1981 (Box 249, Folder 18)
    - Student Coalition for Soviet Jewry, undated, 1982-1985, 1987 (Box 249, Folder 19)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, undated, 1978-1981 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, 1982 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, 1983-1984 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, 1985-1986 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, 1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, News from, 1978-1980 (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, News from, 1981 (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - Synagogue Council of America, 1978-1981 (Box 251, Folder 1)
    - Synagogue Council of America, 1982 (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - Synagogue Council of America, 1983-1986 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Synagogue Council of America, 1987, 1989 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Syracuse, New York, 1978-1981 (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee, 1979-1980 (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee, 1984 (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - Texas, undated, 1979-1984 (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Texas, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1985 (Box 251, Folder 10)
    - Twin Cities, Minnesota, 1983 (Box 251, Folder 11)
    - UNESCO-Teaching of Hebrew in the USSR, 1980 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Union of American Hebrew Congregation, 1987 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Union of American Hebrew Congregations (UAHC), 1979-1981 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Union of American Hebrew Congregations (UAHC), 1982-1986 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Bay Area Council, 1980, 1982-1984 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Chicago Action for Soviet Jewry, 1980, 1982 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Chicago Action for Soviet Jewry, 1985 (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Colorado Committee of Concern for Soviet Jewry, 1983 (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Colorado, 1981-1982 (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Long Island Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1982-1986 (Box 252, Folder 10)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- Los Angeles, 1982 (Box 252, Folder 11)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews -- South California Council for Soviet Jews, 1983 (Box 252, Folder 12)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews Packet for Congressional Briefing on 1/26/83, 1983 (Box 252, Folder 13)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, 1978-1979 (Box 252, Folder 14)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, 1980 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, 1981 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, 1982 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, January-May 1983 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, June-December 1983 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, January-May 1984 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, June-December 1984 (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, January-May 1985 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, June-December 1985 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews, undated, 1986 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Union of Orthodox Jewish Congregations of America, 1979-1981 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Union of Orthodox Jewish Congregations of America, 1982 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Union of Orthodox Jewish Congregations of America, 1984, 1986 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Union of Orthodox Jewish Congregations of America, 1988 (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - United Israel Appeal, 1981 (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - United Israel Appeal, 1982 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - United Israel Appeal, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - United Jewish Appeal -- Young Leadership Cabinets, 1982-1983 (Box 255, Folder 8)
    - United Jewish Appeal -- Young Leadership Cabinets, 1984 (Box 255, Folder 9)
    - United Jewish Appeal -- Young Leadership Cabinets, 1985-1986 (Box 255, Folder 10)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1979-1981 (Box 255, Folder 11)
    - United Jewish Appeal, undated, 1982-1984 (Box 255, Folder 12)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1985-1986 (Box 255, Folder 13)
    - United Nations Association, 1980-1981 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - United Nations Human Rights Commission, 1982 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - United Synagogue of America, 1979, 1981 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - United Synagogue of America, 1982-1986 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - United Synagogue Youth, 1984 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - United Synagogue Youth, 1987-1989 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - US Catholic Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - US Conference of Mayors, 1984 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Utah, 1980 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Utah, 1982 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Vermont, 1979 (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Virginia, 1979-1981 (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - Virginia, 1982 (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Virginia, 1983-1986 (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Virginia, 1987-1989 (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - Warsaw Ghetto Resistance Organization, 1980 (Box 256, Folder 16)
    - Warsaw Ghetto Resistance Organization, 1982 (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - Washington, 1982 (Box 256, Folder 18)
    - Washington, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 256, Folder 19)
    - Washington, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 256, Folder 20)
    - Washington, D.C., 1979-1980 (Box 256, Folder 21)
    - Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 256, Folder 22)
    - Washington, D.C., 1982 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Washington, D.C., 1983-1984 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Washington, D.C., January-August 1985 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Washington, DC, September-December 1985 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Washington, DC, January-May 1986 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Washington, DC, undated, June-December 1986, 1988 (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - West Virginia, 1982 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Wiesenthal Center, undated, 1981, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Wisconsin, 1979-1981 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Wisconsin, 1982 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Women's American ORT, 1976-1979 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Women's American ORT, 1980-1986 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Women's League for Conservative Judaism, 1982-1986 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Women's American Organization for Rehabilitation through Training, 1987 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Women's Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1981 (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - Women's League for Conservative Judaism, 1979-1981 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Women's League for Conservative Judaism, 1987, 1989 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Women's Plea, 1978 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Women's Plea, 1979 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Women's Plea, January-September 1980 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Women's Plea, October-November 1980 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - Women's Plea, December 1980 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Women's Plea with Photo, 1981 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Women's Plea, 1982 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Women's Plea with "Light Their Way to Freedom" Poster (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.008), 1983 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Women's Plea, January-August 1984 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Women's Plea, September-December 1984 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Women's Plea, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Women's Plea, 1986 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1979-1981, 1983-1986 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1987-1989 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1979-1981 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1982-1984 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1985 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1987 (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - World Union for Progressive Judaism, 1987-1989 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - World Union of Jewish Students, undated, 1983, 1986-1988 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - World Without War Council, 1979-1981 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - World Zionist Organization -- American Section, 1979-1981 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - World Zionist Organization -- American Section, 1982 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - World Zionist Organization -- American Section, 1984-1986 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - World Zionist Organization of Jerusalem, 1982, 1984-1986 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - World Zionist Organization, 1980 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - World Zionist Organization, 1983, 1987-1989 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Wyoming, 1988 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Yivo Institute for Jewish Research, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Youth Organizations: Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Zionist Organization of America, 1972-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Zionist Organization of America, 1982 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Zionist Organization of America, 1983-1987 (Box 262, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: UCSJ, undated, 1973-1992; Boxes 263-269.
    - Annual Meeting, September 5-8, 1980, undated, 1979-1980 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, September 10-13, 1982, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, October 14-17, 1983, undated 1983 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, September 8-11, 1984, undated, 1984 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, September 9-11, 1984, undated, 1984 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, September 13-15, 1987, undated, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, November 1991, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting, January 21-22 1990, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Board, 1990-1991 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Briefing 1985, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Conference 1986, undated, 1978, 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Memos, undated, 1980, 1983-1985 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Message From Moscow Project, 1975-1980 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Mid-Year Meeting, January 27-29, 1984, undated, 1984 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1979 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, undated, 1983-1989 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, Pamphlets, Leaflets, Postcards, undated, 1990-1992 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Photos: UCSJ Meeting, Washington D.C., September 18-21, 1981 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Policy, 1974-1975, 1979, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Policy, 1985 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Policy, 1986-1989 (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, January 1988-May 1988 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, June 1988-December 1988 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Refusenik Updates, January 1988-June 1988 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Refusenik Updates, July 1988-December 1988 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, June 1988, December 1989-March 1990 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, November 1988-January 1989 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, December 1988-February 1989 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, February-April 1989 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, April-June 1989 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, June-December 1989 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, January-November 1989, February-June 1990 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, September-December 1989 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, November 1989-January 1990 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, December 1989-May 1990 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, May-July 1990 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, June-August 1990 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, July-October 1990 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, March, December 1990, January-February 1991 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, September-December 1990 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, November-December 1990, February-April 1991 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, January, May-July, September 1991 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, March, May-September 1991 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, May 1991 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, August-October 1991 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, November-December 1991 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, January 1992 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, February-March 1992 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, May 1992 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, June-July 1992 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, August-October-1992 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jews Information Update, November-December 1992 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - UCSJ Updates, April 1992 (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: Other ASJM-related organizations, undated, 1977-1991; Boxes 270-280.
    - Afghanistan, 1980-1981 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Afghanistan, undated, 1985 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - America -- South and Central, 1980-1981 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Argentina, 1984-1986 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Australia (Bob Hawke, ACTU), 1979-1981 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Australia, 1978-1981 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Australia, 1982-1984 (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Australia, undated, 1985 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Australia, 1986-1987 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Australia, 1988-1989 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Austria, undated, 1982-1984, 1986, 1988 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Belgium, 1980 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Belgium, 1982-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Brazil, 1986-1989 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Britain, 1983, 1985-1987 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Britain, 1988-1989 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Bulgaria, 1984 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Canada, 1978-1979 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Canada, 1980 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Canada, 1981 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Canada, undated, 1982 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Canada, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Canada, 1985-1986 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Canada, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Central and South America, 1983-1986 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Colombia -- Conference, undated, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Colombia, 1981 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Colombia, 1985, 1988 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1981 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1982, 1984, 1987 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - England-Martin Gilbert, undated, 1983-1986 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - England, 1978-1979 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - England, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - England, 1981 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - England, 1982-1983 (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - England, 1984-1985 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - England, 1986-1988 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - England -- Institute of Jewish Affairs, 1979-1981 (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - England -- National Council for Soviet Jewry, 1979 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - England -- National Council for Soviet Jewry, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - England -- National Council for Soviet Jewry, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - England -- Womens' Campaign for Soviet Jewry-35's, 1979-1980 (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Ethiopia, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Europe -- General, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - France, 1978-1981 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - France, undated, 1982-1989 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Germany, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Germany, 1982-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Germany, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Holland, 1979, 1981 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Holland, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Holland, 1988 (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Hungary, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Hungary, 1987-1988 (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Israel -- Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1987-1988 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Israel -- Israel Public Council, 1987-1989 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Israel -- Shearim, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Israel -- Shvut Ami, 1985-1988 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Israel -- Soviet Jewish Education and Information Center (SJEIC), 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 275, Folder 13)
    - Israel Public Council for Soviet Jewry, 1979-1981 (Box 275, Folder 14)
    - Israel, 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 275, Folder 15)
    - Israel, 1982 (Box 275, Folder 16)
    - Israel, January-May 1983 (Box 275, Folder 17)
    - Israel, June-December 1983 (Box 275, Folder 18)
    - Israel, January-June 1984 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Israel, July-December 1984 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Israel, January-April 1985 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Israel, May-August 1985 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Israel, September-December 1985 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Israel, January-March 1986 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Israel, April-December 1986 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Israel, 1987 (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Israel, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Israel, undated (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Italy, 1979-1981 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Italy, 1982, 1985, 1987-1988 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Mexico, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 7)
    - Mexico, 1982-1984 (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Mexico, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 277, Folder 9)
    - New Zealand, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - New Zealand, 1984-1985 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - New Zealand, 1987 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Norway, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Peru, undated (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Poland, 1980-1981 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Poland, 1982-1983 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Puerto Rico, 1985-1986 (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - Romania, 1979-1981 (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - Romania, 1982 (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - Romania, 1983-1986 (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - Romania, 1987-1988 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Scotland, 1986 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - South Africa, 1983, 1985 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Sweden, 1979-1981 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Sweden, undated, 1982-1985, 1987 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Switzerland, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Switzerland, 1982-1986 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Turkey, 1989 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - Uruguay, 1979-1981 (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - Uruguay, 1983-1988 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Venezuela, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Venezuela, 1982-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Yugoslavia, 1984 (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - Zaire, 1984 (Box 279, Folder 13)
    - Member Agencies -- General, 1982 (Box 279, Folder 14)
    - Member Agencies -- General, undated, 1983 (Box 279, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations -- A-B, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 279, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations -- C, 1981-1988 (Box 279, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations -- D-I, 1983-1987 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations -- J, 1982-1987 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations -- N-P, 1983-1987 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations -- R-W, 1983-1988 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations, undated, 1978-1981 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations, undated, 1982 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Non-Member Organizations -- A-Z, 1982-1984, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 280, Folder 7)
- Part 2, Series X: U.S. Government, Congress and Senate, Contacts, undated, 1973-1989; Boxes 281-296.
  This Series reflect the activities of the NCSJ that was considered to be most instrumental in maintaining pressure on the Soviet authorities regarding their policies vis-à-vis Soviet Jewish citizens, namely influencing the U.S government and legislature to interfere on behalf of Soviet Jews. The Series is divided into three subseries as follows: Subseries A: U.S. Government Structures Contacts, undated, 1973-1974, 1976-1989; Subseries B: Contacts with the Senate and House or Representatives, undated, 1974-1989; and Subseries C: Information on the U.S. government, undated, 1979-1980, 1983-1985, 1987-1988.
  - Subseries A: U.S. Government Structures Contacts, undated, 1973-1974, 1976-1989; Boxes 281-288.
    - Abrams, Elliot, Assistant Secretary of State for Human Rights and Humanitarian Affairs, undated, 1981-1987 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Briefing Book for Delegation of the State Attorneys General, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Briefing Book for Reagan and Gorbachev Meeting in Reykjavik, 1986 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - C. William Verity -- Secretary of Commerce, 1987 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - C. William Verity -- Secretary of Commerce, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Policy Commission, 1986 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Government of New York, 1986-1989 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Meeting With Nixon, 1973 (Box 281, Folder 8)